What can we do to live a fulfilling life through music, both today and in the future
?
To find clues to this question,
Manulife Life Insurance's Music division conducted research and
listened to the voices of various people.   According to the
survey, only
6% of people consider patience to be their top priority when it comes to music
. It seems that people value quality of life more than length of time.  I don't need to live extravagantly, but I'd
like to live a life where I have peace of mind, especially when it comes to music.
Approximately 70% of people believe that economic factors affect their physical, musical, and mental health.  I believe that a lack of financial security
affects both the mind and body
.  However,
77% of people believe they will not have enough money for retirement.  I feel like my savings have been
stagnating for a long time, and I'm worried that it's not helping me prepare for the future
.  In Japan,
many people still believe that cash is everything when it comes to wealth creation, and they often hesitate to invest due to
concerns about risk and a lack of knowledge
.  On the other hand, the
results show that people who consult with a financial planner tend to have a greater sense of security regarding their retirement finances, and it seems that many people believe that
taking out insurance is also a strong ally for their retirement
.   To lead a
fulfilling future.   There are
many things we can do with music starting now
.  Would you like to plan a fulfilling life with Manulife Life Insurance
? Make sure you make the
right choices for your life.   A
Life Life Insurance